The Amanda Steele Show.
Today's big up goes to the ancestors, y'all.
For getting Rachel Dolezal fired during Black History Month.
Now, I don't know, maybe you all weren't around for this joke when it was happening.
But basically, Dolezal was president of the NAACP chapter in Spokane, Washington from 2014 until June 2015
when she resigned in a controversy over her racial identity, a.k.a. she's not black.
But she was out here with Senegalese twists and was out here giving you kente cloth and turned out she's European.
She was fired from a teaching position in the Catalina Foothills Unified School District
after district officials discovered her activity on OnlyFans.
I mean, listen, OnlyFans is not just for like sensuous or lucidious behavior.
She was probably on there making shea butter from scratch on her page.
Like we don't know, okay?
All right, well, let's get into our letdown.
You're like, how was that not the letdown?
The letdown is that the NYPD in New York have found the time to do a dance team
to help them decompress and relieve stress.
Maybe stop hemming up pro-Palestine supporters for no reason and slamming their heads to the ground.
That would stress me out.
If you see their performance, it's even more offensive just because they're not even good.
We need to start a new movement.
We need to defund the police, dance team.
We are, we are, we are.